Hint: He and Darth Vader
are tied for number two.
(Howard:)Sorry, I couldn't hang with you.
I had a date with Bernadette.
(Raj:)I know. I saw the tweet.
(Howard:)-So, what did you end up doing?
-Not much. Nuked a burrito...
...prayed to Hindu god Urvashi
your bowels'd loosen...
(Raj:)...and your penis would droop
like a willow tree.
(Leonard:)-You seen Sheldon?
-No.
-Is he still mad about the Super Collider?
-Yeah, he thinks I betrayed him.
(Leonard:)What would you guys do
if you were me?
(Howard:)I'd take Sheldon to Switzerland.
(Leonard:)-Seriously?
-Absolutely. And I'd leave him there.
(Raj:)What the hell is that?
(Leonard:)Uh, let's see.
Yep, 30 pieces of silverware.
[RECORDER PLAYING]